{
    "id": "a444da8d8f5d438dad0912980f4c7e99",
    "title": "Lie, Lay, Less, Few",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "62decfb081844040b6e61f805828ded1",
            "title": "Lay, Lie, Less, Fewer",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "A turtle ………………………… many eggs at one time.",
                    "description": "Lay means produce or bear. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "lies",
                        "lays",
                        "lains"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. the cartons one on top of the other.",
                    "description": "To lay something is to put it down carefully.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Lay",
                        "Lie",
                        "Lain"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………. the plates on the table.",
                    "description": "Laid is the past tense of lay.",
                    "answers": [
                        "lain",
                        "laid",
                        "lied"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was angry with me because I ……………………… to her.",
                    "description": "Lied is the past tense of lie. To lie is to say something untrue.",
                    "answers": [
                        "laid",
                        "lain",
                        "lied"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please ……………………….. down.",
                    "description": "Lie can mean be horizontal.",
                    "answers": [
                        "lie",
                        "lay",
                        "laid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………….. down and closed my eyes but I could not sleep.",
                    "description": "When lie means be down, lay is its past tense.",
                    "answers": [
                        "lie",
                        "lay",
                        "lain"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sam earns the most money in our family James earns …………………….",
                    "description": "The least is the opposite of the most. It is used with uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "the least",
                        "the lowest",
                        "the fewest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The essay with ………………………. errors is not always the best.",
                    "description": "With plural nouns we use fewest and with uncountable nouns we use least.",
                    "answers": [
                        "the least",
                        "the fewest",
                        "the lowest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She always arrives when you …………………………. expect it.",
                    "description": "When least is used as an adverb, it is used without the.",
                    "answers": [
                        "least",
                        "the least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am ………………………….. interested in this offer.",
                    "description": "Both expressions mean the same. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "not in the least",
                        "not at all",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………….. people cook their own meals these days.",
                    "description": "We use fewer with plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Fewer",
                        "Less",
                        "Lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The most effective way to lose weight is to eat ……………………… food.",
                    "description": "Less is the comparative of little.",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "lesser",
                        "least"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}